38 Adjective - Learn Swedish with Marie
There are subtitles in many languages.
Hello everyone!
Welcome!
Today I will go through 38 adjectives.
I will tell you how they are bent at one-word, by a word and in plural words.
What is good is that you can also figure out adverbs.
Because in Swedish, the adverb looks the same as in one-word.
It's good, is not it!
Then you can already all adverbs.
Feel free to say (me).
I exaggerate the pronunciation.
It's a brave girl.
We have to make a brave decision!
hungry, hungry, hungry
A hungry lion.
The kids are hungry!
starving, starving starved (I've spelled the picture in the picture !!!)
A starved lion.
The children are starved!
happy, cheerful, happy
It's great with happy people!
sorry, sad, sad